# **MERT ÖZLER**

Bio: I was born on October 6, 1999 in Bursa. I've been interested in software since high school. I have a passion for social sciences and dancing. In my spare time, I write articles about my research.

Goal: I aim to be a backend developer. My long-term career goal is to be a software architect.

## **Experience**

### **Software Engineer Intern**

#### Egebarkod Yazılım Ltd.Şti

February 2022 – May 2022

- .NET CORE Web Apps
- Entity Framework, N-Layer Architecture
- ElasticSearch, Kibana, Serilog, Hangfire
- RESTful APIs

## **Software Engineer Intern**

#### Yeni Nesil Yazılım Teknolojileri San. Tic. Ltd. Şti

July 2021 - August 2022

- I developed android and web applications with Java
- MVVM architecture, Retrofit, .NET ve REST API used.
- I learned about ERP software, I made improvements to the project used by the company.

# **Education**

## Muğla Sıtkı Koçman Üniversitesi

2018 - 2022

Information System Engineering

• 2.98 GPA

## M. Kemal Coşkunöz Endüstri Meslek Lisesi

2013 - 2017

**Database Programming** 

- OOP and SQL
- · Developing an inventory tracking program with .NET

## **Projects**

## **▼** Graduation Project: Pandemic Management System

In my graduation project, which was deemed worthy of evaluation within the scope of TUBITAK 2229-A, it is aimed to simulate the positive and negative conditions that the pandemic will create with real data by using data science techniques. In this way, it will be possible for the necessary authorities to make the right decision. The project is in development until June 2022.



## **Contact Details**



meozler@gmail.com



0534 598 37 99



<u>LinkedIn</u>



<u>Github</u>

## **Talents**

- Programming Languages- Python, C#, Java, JS, CSS, HTML, Node.js
- Databases MySQL, SQL, PostgreSQL, Firebase
- Framework .NET, Bootstrap, React

MERT ÖZLER 1

## **▼** Company Support Manangment System

It was developed with .NET 5.0 with N-Layer Architecture architecture. The project includes features such as Serilog and Hangfire. The project makes it easier to support companies. Management has become easier with admin, staff and customer panels.

## **▼** MusicParty

MusicParty is developed with React and Node.js. In this application, it is aimed for users to listen to music and socialize simultaneously via Spotify API.

## **▼** HiChat

HiChat is a messaging application. Developed with React Native. Messages and user information are saved with Firebase.

## **▼** BlogPanel

BlogPanel is a blog site application. Developed with .NET Core 5.0. User, author and admin panels are made easier to use.

## **▼** BiTaksi Golang Bootcamp Graduation Project

BiTaksi is Turkey's taxi application. In this bootcamp, after training on topics such as DDD, TDD, Clean Code and Design Pattern as well as golang training, I made a prototype of the BiTaksi application as a graduation project.

MERT ÖZLER 2